###### About Us

    * Privacy Policy

###### Related Links

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Modified: October 9, 2024_

CustomInk, LLC ("Custom Ink", “we” or “us”) understands that security and privacy are important issues for users of our services available at [www.customink.com](https://www.customink.com/about/privacy) (the "Site"). The following Privacy Policy (this "Policy") describes how we collect, use and share the information that we gather about the users of our Site.

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site. By using our Site, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information, including Personal Information (defined below), as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site is subject to this Policy and our [User Agreement](https://www.customink.com/about/user_agreement).

This Policy may change from time to time (see [Changes to this Policy](#12)). Your continued use of our Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Policy periodically for updates. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact us as set forth in the Contacting Custom Ink section below.

Information we collect
----------------------

We may collect information about you, including information that can identify you as an individual (“Personal Information”), (i) directly from you, (ii) automatically through your use of our Site, and (iii) from third parties. We may combine the information we collect about you from these various sources.

* **Information we collect directly from you.** Depending on how you use our Site, you may provide us with Personal Information such as your name, email address, phone number, credit or debit card information and shipping or billing address. We will also collect any other information that you choose to provide to us through our Site (e.g., contents of messages you send to us through our Site).
* **Content that you provide.** You may upload comments, reviews, graphics, photos or other materials to the Site ("Content"). If you post Content on our Site, the Content (e.g., t-shirt designs or photos submitted as part of a contest), as well as other information (e.g., user name or profile picture), may be available to all visitors to our Site. We cannot prevent such Content or information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, our [User Agreement](https://www.customink.com/about/user_agreement), the law, or your personal privacy.
* **Information we collect about you from third parties.** We may collect information about you from third parties. For example, we may collect demographics information from public sources and from third-party data and analytics companies. In addition, we may collect information about you from other Custom Ink users (e.g., if one user ships a package to another user).
* **Information we collect automatically through your use of our Site.** We may automatically collect information about your use of our Site and your orders, including but not limited to your Internet protocol (“IP”) address; the type of web browser you are using; the website that led you to our Site; the website you visit after leaving our Site; the pages you view on our Site; the dates and times you access our Site; and information about any orders you place, such as your order identification number, items ordered and the cost of your order.

How we use your information
---------------------------

Custom Ink may use your information, including Personal Information and/or Content, for the following purposes:

* **Providing our services.** To facilitate your orders and administer your account; to respond to your questions or requests; to provide you with news or other information we think may interest you; to communicate with you about your account, orders or use of our Site or for other informational purposes; to improve our services; and for other account or customer support-related purposes. Please note that we use your email address to save and identify your products designs on our Site, and so please be aware that your designs can be viewed on the Site by anyone who enters your email address.
* **Marketing and advertising.** To provide you with special offers, product information and other marketing or promotional communications from Custom Ink or from other third parties. We may provide marketing or advertising to you in a variety of ways, including through our Site, via email, via SMS (text) message (provided you have expressly opted in to receive text communications from us) or on other third-party websites (e.g., using [Google Customer Match](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6299717) or [Facebook Ads](https://www.facebook.com/business/products/ads)). See our [Online advertising](#6) and [Your choices](#7) sections below for more information.
* **Research and analytics.** To analyze how customers use our Site, services and products; to analyze how customers interact with marketing or other communications we send to them; and for other research, analytical and statistical purposes. This research may include creating profiles to help us analyze or predict your personal preferences or interests for marketing purposes.
* **Protecting rights and interests.** To investigate, protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Custom Ink, our customers or the public; to investigate or enforce perceived violations of our [User Agreement](https://www.customink.com/about/user_agreement) or this Policy; as evidence in litigation in which we are involved; and for fraud protection and credit risk reduction purposes.

How we share your information
-----------------------------

Custom Ink may share your information, including Personal Information and/or Content, with the following types of third parties:

* **Service providers.** Custom Ink may share your information with third-party service providers, vendors, agents, contractors or others who perform functions on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to process your orders, deliver packages or send mail. We enter into written agreements with these third-party service providers requiring them to provide the same level of protection for your Personal Information as provided under this Policy and limiting their use of your Personal Information to the specified services provided on our behalf.
* **Corporate affiliates.** Custom Ink may share your information with any current or future Custom Ink parent company, affiliate or subsidiary.
* **Certain other unaffiliated third parties.** Subject to applicable laws, Custom Ink may share your information directly with certain third party organizations with which Custom Ink has entered into contractual relationships and that make Custom Ink products available to you, including so they may send you marketing offers directly. For example, we may share your information with (i) fundraising organizations that launch campaigns to raise funds by selling Custom Ink products, and (ii) sponsors of online stores that sell Custom Ink products to their users (e.g., employees of a company-sponsored online store). The information that we share with such third parties may include, without limitation, your email address, billing address, shipping address and order information (e.g., total price). Your information will be protected in accordance with the privacy policies of those organizations.

Custom Ink may also share your information, including Personal Information and/or Content, in the following cases:

* **Protecting rights and interests.** Custom Ink may share your information with law enforcement agencies and others as we deem appropriate to investigate, protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Custom Ink, our customers or the public; to investigate or enforce perceived violations of our [User Agreement](https://www.customink.com/about/user_agreement) or this Policy; as evidence in litigation in which we are involved; and for fraud protection and credit risk reduction purposes.
* **Sale or acquisition of assets.** Custom Ink may share your information if we become involved in a transaction involving the sale of our assets, such as a merger or acquisition, if we are transferred to another company, in the event of a bankruptcy, or as part of any other business transfer. If the surviving entity in such a transaction is not Custom Ink, the surviving entity may use your information pursuant to its own privacy policies, which may be different from this Policy.
* **Legal compliance.** Custom Ink may share your information to comply with laws, regulations, legal process (e.g., a warrant or subpoena) or guidance; and to respond to governmental requests (e.g., requests from a regulator).
* **Aggregate or anonymous information.** Custom Ink may share anonymized or aggregated information about Custom Ink users to third parties without restriction. For example, we may share anonymized or aggregated information to inform a third party’s decision on whether to place advertisements on our Site or on other websites. These companies may use such information about your visits to the Site and other websites to provide advertisements on the Site and other websites.

If you opt in to receiving SMS (text) messages from us, we will not share your opt-in with any third party for purposes unrelated to providing you with our services relating to those text messages. We may share your Personal Information, including your SMS opt-in or consent status, with third parties that help us provide our text messaging services, including but not limited to platform providers, phone companies, and any other vendors who assist us in the delivery of text messages.

Cookies and other tracking mechanisms
-------------------------------------

We may automatically collect information about you through the use of common online information-gathering tools, as well as new tracking technologies that develop as technology evolves. The tools that we or our service providers may use to collect information about you include the following:

* **Cookies.** A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser to help the website remember and customize your visit. For example, we use cookies to help us to tailor our Site to you, remember your orders, keep you logged into your account, and compile statistics about Site usage. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block or disable cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features (e.g., you may not be able to stay logged into your account).
* **Web beacons/clear GIFs.** Clear graphics interchange format images (“GIFs”) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are embedded invisibly on web pages or in emails. We or our service providers may use clear GIFs (also known as web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags) in connection with our Site to track the activities of visitors to our Site, help us manage content and compile statistics about usage of our Site. We or our service providers may also use clear GIFs in emails to our users, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed and track whether our emails are forwarded.
* **LSOs.** We may also use local storage objects (“LSOs”) to store your Site preferences and to personalize your visit. LSOs are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored. Typically, you cannot control, delete or disable the acceptance of LSOs through your web browser. For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash LSOs, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). We may use applications, servers and other technology provided by third-party companies, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), to help us improve our Site, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and information-gathering tools, such as web beacons or LSOs, to perform their services.

Do not track disclosure
-----------------------

Our Site does not respond to do not track signals (e.g., the Mozilla Firefox [Do Not Track feature](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/dnt/)), though you may be able to disable certain tracking as discussed above (e.g., by disabling cookies). There is still no universally accepted standard regarding tracking. For more information about do not track signals, please click [here](https://allaboutdnt.com/).

Online advertising
------------------

We use third-party marketing or advertising companies (e.g., [Google Customer Match](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6299717)) to serve advertisements on our Site and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms). These third parties use technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking), which allows targeting advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Advertisements may be targeted to you based on the pages you view on our Site or on third-party websites, as well as other information that they may have about you. These third parties may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information, including Personal Information, about you, as permitted under our agreements with such third parties.

Users in the United States may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having information used by [DAA companies](http://www.aboutads.info/participating/). You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having information used by [NAI members](http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating-networks).

Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or the NAI [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-based content or advertisements to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Site or on other websites. Please note that even if you opt out, you may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the NAI’s website at [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The service providers we use for online advertising may change. However, for your convenience, here are the opt outs for some of the advertising service providers we use as of the “Last Modified” date of this Policy:

Your choices
------------

* **Account information.** If you ever wish to access your Personal Information, update your Personal Information or cancel your account, please submit a [request](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ad37f637-4936-48fb-9de5-eacfd28c9739/81ffeefa-aa44-4b28-9a0e-e8710790f056). Please note that we may maintain copies of your information and Content even after you have updated the information or canceled your account.
* **Communications from Custom Ink.** We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you, about Custom Ink and other third-party information and offers. In the event you do not wish to receive such emails from Custom Ink, you may opt out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive or by [requesting](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ad37f637-4936-48fb-9de5-eacfd28c9739/81ffeefa-aa44-4b28-9a0e-e8710790f056) that you no longer receive communications from us. It may take us up to ten (10) business days to process your opt out request. Even if you have opted out of receiving marketing and promotional emails from us, we may still send you transactional emails, such as emails about your account or the services you have requested from us. We may also send you marketing or promotional SMS (text) messages, but only if you have expressly opted in to receive such communications. You may opt out of receiving text messages from us at any time. To opt out, please follow the instructions provided in the text message (e.g., replying with "STOP"). Upon receipt of your opt-out request, we will promptly remove your mobile number from our marketing text message list.
* **Communications from Third Parties.** You may also opt out of our sharing your information with third parties for their own marketing purposes on a going forward basis by filling out a [request](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ad37f637-4936-48fb-9de5-eacfd28c9739/81ffeefa-aa44-4b28-9a0e-e8710790f056). Please note that once we have shared your information with a third party, such information is subject to that third party’s privacy policies and practices.
* **Online advertising.** Please see our Online advertising section above for more information about your choices regarding online interest-based advertising.

International transfers
-----------------------

Our Site is maintained in the United States. The information we collect from you through our services may be transferred to, and stored and processed in the United States and other destinations outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or other country in which you are located. This includes processing by us, our affiliates, our third party service companies and other third parties as described in this Policy. You explicitly consent and agree to such transfer, storing and/or processing of your Personal Information outside the EEA or other country in which you are located. You understand that data stored in the United States may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the United States. The United States may not have data protection laws that are as comprehensive or protective as those in your country of residence; however, our collection, storage and use of your Personal Information will at all times be in accordance with this Policy.

Your European privacy rights
----------------------------

If you are a resident of the European Union or the United Kingdom, you have certain additional rights with respect to your Personal information under, respectively, the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (the “EU GDPR”) and the Data Protection, Privacy and Electronic Communications (Amendments etc.) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 (the “UK GDPR”) (collectively, the “GDPR”), including the following:

* The right of access to your Personal Information.
* The right to rectify your Personal Information if it is incorrect or incomplete.
* The right to have your Personal Information erased (“right to be forgotten”) if certain grounds are met.
* The right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Information at any time (if our processing is based on consent).
* The right to object to our processing of your Personal Information (if processing is based on legitimate interests).
* The right to object to our processing of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes.
* The right to receive your Personal Information from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and the right to transmit your Personal Information to another controller without hindrance from us (data portability).

If you are located in the European Union or the United Kingdom and you are or have been our customer, we may send you marketing communications based on our legitimate interests, subject always to your right to opt out of such communications. Further, if you are located in the European Union or the United Kingdom, we will never share your Personal Information with a third party for such third party’s marketing purposes, unless you have specifically consented to us doing so.

You may fill out a request [here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ad37f637-4936-48fb-9de5-eacfd28c9739/81ffeefa-aa44-4b28-9a0e-e8710790f056) to exercise any of the above rights. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity, and in some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your Personal Information.

Furthermore, if you believe that our processing of your Personal Information is inconsistent with your data protection rights under the GDPR and we have not adequately addressed your concerns, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority of your country.

For purposes of the GDPR, we are a “controller” and you are a “data subject.”

Your California privacy rights
------------------------------

If you are a California resident, California law provides you with additional rights regarding our use of your Personal Information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit [CUSTOM INK PRIVACY NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS.](https://www.customink.com/about/ccpa)

Your Virginia privacy rights
----------------------------

If you are a Virginia resident, Virginia law provides you with additional rights regarding our use of your Personal Information. Specifically, you may exercise the following rights:

* To confirm whether or not we are processing your Personal Information and to access such Personal Information.
* To correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, taking into account the nature of the Personal Information and the purposes of the processing of your Personal Information.
* To delete Personal Information that you provide or that we obtain about you.
* To obtain a copy of your Personal Information that you previously provided us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit your Personal Information to another entity without hindrance, where the processing is carried out by automated means.
* To opt out of the processing of your Personal Information for purposes of targeted advertising, the sale of your Personal Information and profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you.

To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before complying with your request. If we decline to take action in response to any request that you submit in connection with the rights described above, you may ask that we reconsider our response by sending an email to us at privacy@customink.com. You must ask us to reconsider our decision within 45 days after we send you our decision.

Your Texas privacy rights
-------------------------

If you are a Texas resident, Texas law provides you with additional rights regarding our use of your Personal Information. Specifically, you may exercise the following rights:

* To confirm whether or not we are processing your Personal Information and to access and obtain a copy of such Personal Information.
* To correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, taking into account the nature of the Personal Information and the purposes of the processing of your Personal Information.
* To request that we delete Personal Information that you provide or that we obtain about you.
* To obtain a copy of your Personal Information that you previously provided us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit your Personal Information to another entity without hindrance, where the data is available in a digital format.
* To opt out of the processing of your Personal Information for purposes of targeted advertising, the sale of your Personal Information and profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you.

To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before complying with your request. If we decline to take action in response to any request that you submit in connection with the rights described above, you may ask that we reconsider our response by sending an email to us at [privacy@customink.com](mailto:privacy@customink.com). You must ask us to reconsider our decision within 45 days after we send you our decision.

Children’s privacy
------------------

Our Site is not targeted to children under thirteen (13) years of age and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a child under 13, we will promptly take measures to delete that Personal Information from our systems. In the case of residents of the European Union and the United Kingdom, we do not collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 16 except with parental consent, subject to an EU member state providing by law for a lower age (not below 13 years).

External links
--------------

Our Site may contain links to other websites. Your use of an external website is subject to and governed by the terms and policies of that website. Custom Ink is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit.

Security
--------

We have implemented technical and organizational measures, appropriate to the risk, to protect your information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and unauthorized disclosure or access. For example, we limit internal access to our servers and have physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards in place that are designed to protect your information. However, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted through our Site. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any such information, and you provide such information at your own risk.

You can also take steps to help protect your information. For example, if you have an account with us, you should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your account by, among other things, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess and keeping your log-in and password private.

Data retention
--------------

We retain your Personal Information, if provided by you through our Site, for as long as your inquiry is active (as determined by us) and for a reasonable time thereafter, or if applicable, for as long as you remain on our marketing list. We also may retain your Personal Information for a longer period of time on the basis of our legitimate interests in providing our Services to you or as necessary to comply with our tax and legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Even if we delete some or all of your Personal Information, we may continue to retain and use aggregated or anonymous data previously collected so that it can no longer be used for personal identification and/or anonymize or aggregate your Personal Information. Please note that we will not be liable for disclosures of your data due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.

Changes to this Policy
----------------------

This Policy was last updated as of the “Last Modified” date above. Custom Ink may modify this Policy at any time and will post any updates to our Site. We therefore encourage you to review this page frequently for any changes.

Contacting Custom Ink
---------------------

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, or to exercise your rights under this Policy, please contact us using the information below.

Custom Ink, LLC  
2910 District Ave.  
Fairfax VA, 22031  
703-891-2205  
[Click Here](https://www.customink.com/remove) to unsubscribe from marketing  
[Click Here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ad37f637-4936-48fb-9de5-eacfd28c9739/81ffeefa-aa44-4b28-9a0e-e8710790f056) for privacy and marketing removals  
Email [privacy@customink.com](mailto:privacy@customink.com) for all other requests

###### Contact Us

* Talk to a Real Person  
    7 Days a Week
* 8am-Midnight ET Mon-Fri
* 10am-6pm ET Saturday
* 10am-6pm ET Sunday

* Headset Ico [800-293-4232](tel:800-293-4232)
* Email Icon Send us an Email

Custom Ink is your source for [custom t-shirts](https://www.customink.com/products/t-shirts/4).  

* Do Not Sell My Information

© 2024 CustomInk, LLC. All rights reserved.
